[{"answer": "Certainly in this area, Piers, there is a mood of frustration.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "What is the real mood, do you think?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "You know, I have been talking to a lot of people out here, and they are of two minds.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Do they care enough about this election to try to get to a polling booth, even if they could?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, I -- those that I talk to know that the president came out to the area, those supportive of him and even those who aren't -- who aren't.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Do the people there feel strongly that the president should have come to where you are?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Things are tough.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "How are things in Newark right now?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "That seems so blatantly partisan, and during this time we in the tristate area are really suffering, we just don't need this kind of language.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Look, I think that people are starting to see the truth of what the president has done.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "What do you think in the end will be the determining factor?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Yes!", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "I just want to turn around and say, are you guys going to vote in this election?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "We are fired up.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Where do you think you really are?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, that's why I think the country's going to make a change.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "If you can't beat an incumbent president when unemployment is just nearly at 8 percent still and the debt's risen by $5 trillion, to $16 interest, it's pretty much a disaster for the Republican Party, isn't it?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "What do you make of what he said, and do you believe that the administration has a case to answer?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "You know, I guess personally, that would mean a lot to me, but you know what, I'm pretty proud of this country.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What would it mean to you personally to get the first ever Mormon president of the United States?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "No, you don't.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "So -- I don't have to stay here very long, though, do I?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "\"The Good Wife.\"", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Can we talk politics?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Mostly loved it, yes.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "People either loved it or they hated it, you know that?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Were you pleased with the reaction?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "It's a combination of things.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Why is it so close?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Not amongst young people.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "I mean, I have asked a lot of people this, whether America's become more -- actually been more racist since Barack Obama become president than less, and I think most people believe that it has actually become slightly more racist, it has brought out more racism?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I don't think he has been.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Why has Obama been so curiously lackluster in this campaign?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "OK, so he wasn't.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "How do you persuade those people who just think, you know what, he has done OK, but he wasn't the messiah after all?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "First of all, I just want to say that we just got word that football ran late tonight, so \"The Good Wife\" is not starting until 9:35.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Back now, Michael Moore, what did you make of that?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "There's no point to it.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Cheap shot, or did it have a little point to it?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "The point is they are building Jeeps in China for the Chinese is the point?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "If they were building any cars in China for the American market, would you feel differently?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Do you think it could go the wrong way?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Well, look, I know from our campaign's perspective, we feel pretty good about where things are.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "How do you see the map of Tuesday night really evolving based on where things are right now?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Piers, I don't know that I would agree with the fact that, you know, for four years minus two days he has been lackluster but he has been fired up and ready to go the last two days.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Why has he been so apparently comparatively lackluster until really the last few days?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Well, look, I look at the last 32 months of jobs reports, and it's been positive private sector job growth, 5.4 million jobs have been created.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Do you accept that?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Well, look, I'm going to tell you why I think Barack Obama and this campaign are going to win, because I think we have a better message.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Would you go along with any of those four things?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Good to be with you.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Grover, how are you?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I think Romney's going to win.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "You feeling confident you're going to win?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Someone who looks pretty happy at the moment is Mitt Romney.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "How are they going to make it better if they are happy with the lousy job record that they have had?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "The interesting thing that's going on, and I think it would be bad for the country, but the modern Republican Party, we have 29 Republican governors.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "If Mitt Romney can't beat a president who in four years has seen the debt rise by $5 trillion, to $16 trillion, has seen unemployment remain pretty much at 8 percent, that is a catastrophe for the Republicans, isn't it?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121104pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Can we assume, Marjorie, do you think, that if Romney was to lose, all the blame will be laid squarely on Hurricane Sandy with a dash of Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 533}]